声明：本字幕由YYeTs人人影视字幕组原创翻译制作
禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
欢迎登录人人影视论坛交流 下载 在线观看 www.YYeTs.net
■
=====本字幕由以下成员荣誉制作 感谢他们的无私奉献======
翻译：妞妞小宝 paradise 螃蟹 wolfRay
校对：美景 互校时间轴：YY吕伟 leolou
========== 字幕总监制：何何   ==========
-你想去哪?  -出去
Where do you think you're going? out.
和谁?
With who?
他?
Him?
对  你别想阻止我  我恋爱了
Yes, and you can't stop me. I'm in love.
他都可以当你爹啦  emily
He's twice your age, emily.
那又怎样  妈妈?  你是不是嫉妒我啊?
So what, mom? are you jealous?
Emily  等等
Emily, wait a minute.
Emily  听我说!
Emily, listen to me!
Emily!
给我回来  死丫头  现在!
Get back here, young lady, right now!
你阻止不了我的!  我爱他!
You can't stop me! I love him!
Emily!  emily...
Emily! emily--
亲爱的?  亲爱的  能听到我说话吗
Honey? honey, can you hear me?
亲爱的  能听到我说话吗
Honey, can you hear me?
很好  现在试着保持清醒
That's good. try and stay awake now.
一定伤着内脏了
Must be internal.
稳住  不要挡路  脉搏多少!
Keep it steady. out of the way. pulse!
-她在出血  心跳越来越弱了  -我怀孕了
She's bleeding. her heartbeat's dropping fast. I'm pregnant.
-什么  你说什么  -我怀孕了
What? what did you say? I'm pregnant.
五个月...我现在差不多怀孕6个月了
I'm five-- I'm almost six months.
她...她怀孕了
She--she's pregnant.
准备夹钳
Get the clamps ready.
就这样  emily  好姑娘  宝宝的头出来了
That's it, emily. good girl. baby's crowning.
宝宝的头出来了
She's crowning.
再用力啊
Dilated and ready to go.
出来了  太好了
Here we go. that's it.
好的  甜心  就是这样
Okay, sweetheart. all right, there you go.
把你包得又舒服又暖和
Wrap you up nice and warm.
我们现在就把你带走
We'll just take you over here now.
Margaret  帮我把他抱进去好吗
Margaret, would you put him in for me, please?
我的宝宝
My baby.
是个男孩  亲爱的
It's a boy, honey.
他现在很好  只是出来得太早了
He's okay for now. he's just real early.
能给我抱抱吗
Can I hold him?
抱歉  亲爱的  他还太小了
I'm sorry, sweetheart. he's just too little.
现在我们必须把他带走
We have to take him away now.
可是...
But...
叫他...叫他john
Name--name him john.
他的名字叫john!
His name is john!
谁会在丛林中间造一个小屋啊?
Who builds a cabin in the middle of the jungle anyway?
问得好
That's a good question.
那么  是谁造的?
So? how about answering it?
不知道
I don't know.
还有  我们为什么要去那?
And why are we even going there?
因为希望  住在小屋里的那个人
Because hopefully, the man who lives in the cabin
会告诉我们该如何对付
Can tell us what to do
那群要杀我们的人
About the people who are trying to kill us.
我们已经走了一天了  快到那边了吗
We've been walking all day. are we gonna get there soon?
还要多久?
How long?
不知道
I don't know.
我只是跟着他
I've been following him.
什么  你什么意思  什么叫你只是跟着他?
What? what do you mean, you've been following him?
-我都没走在前头  -我不知道那个小屋在哪
I'm not even in front. I have no idea where the cabin is.
-Hugo是最后一个看到小屋的人  -哦  "太棒了"
Hugo's the last one who saw it. oh, this is just awesome.
你觉得我们该怎么办  john?
What do you think we should do, john?
我们扎营吧
We're making camp.
在这么黑的地方还有怪物在附近  外加...  他?
Here in the dark with the monster and... him?
其余的会善待我们的
Well, the rest will do us good.
哥们  那些货船上的家伙回来的话会怎么样?
Dude, what's gonna happen when those freighter guys come back?
我还...
I don't know...
Desmond
Desmond.
直升机来了
The helicopter's here.
好的  把他抬到担架上
All right, get him on the litter.
当心点!
Careful with him!
把他抬到那里  小心点
Get him down over there. be careful.
好的  伙计们  卸下来
Okay, guys, unload it.
快点  抬起来  抬起来  我们走
Come on. pick it up. pick it up. let's go.
这是谁干的?
What did this to him?
黑色的烟柱把他抛到了50英尺的空中...
A black pillar of smoke threw him 50 feet in the air...
内脏都被撕裂出来了
Ripped his guts out.
什么
What?
我要你准确地告诉我岛上到底有多少人
I need you to tell me exactly how many people
以及每个人的方位
Are on that island and where every single one of them is.
我干嘛要告诉你?
And why would I do that?
Keamy!
-你他妈的以为你在干什么  mate?  -你出卖了我
What the hell do you think you're doing, mate? you gave me up.
-什么?  -linus知道我是谁  他知道我的名字
What? linus knew who I was. he knew my name.
他知道我的一切
He knew everything about me.
不  我没有出卖你
No, I'm not the one who gave you up.
那是谁?
Then who did?
啊!  哦!  哦!
Aah! oh! oh!
哦!
Ohh!
知道我是谁吗
Do you know who I am?
什么
What?
我的名字  知道我叫什么吗
My name. do you know my name?
Keamy
Keamy.
Martin keamy
Martin keamy.
是你告诉他的吗
Did you give it to him?
-谁?  -benjamin linus  你把我的名字告诉他了?
Who? benjamin linus-- did you give him my name?
是的
Yeah.
等等  等等!
Wait. wait!
Martin  住手!
Martin, no!
Martin  我们用得着他
Martin, we need him.
只有他能修好发动机
He's the only one who can fix the engines.
你就这么确定?
And what makes you so sure about that?
因为就是他弄坏的
Because he's the one who broke them.
你好啊
Hello there.
你是谁?
Who are you?
我是horace
I'm horace. whew!
你在这干什么?
And what are you doing out here?
哦  造一个...
Oh, building a place--
能给我还有我老婆逃跑的小地方
A little getaway for me and the missus.
不对  我是说
No, I mean,
达摩的工作之余也要歇一歇  知道吗
Sometimes you need a break from the d.i., you know?
达摩组织
The dharma initiative?
我说的你听不懂  对吧?
I'm not making any sense, am i?
对
No.
那可能是因为我已经死了12年了
That's probably because I've been dead for 12 years.
喂
Hello there.
你得找到我  john
You gotta find me, john.
你得找到我
You gotta find me.
当你找到我后  你就会找到他的
And when you do, you'll find him.
谁?
Who?
Jacob
Jacob.
他已经等了你很久了  伙计
He's been waiting for you a real long time, man.
我叫horace
I'm horace.
祝你成功  john
Godspeed, john.
Hugo
Hugo.
果甜三明治
Mallomars.
醒醒  hugo
Wake up, hugo.
唔?  啊?  怎么了?
Hmm? huh? what?
该起来了  我们要出发了
Time to get up. we're gonna get going.
-哥们  我记得你说不知道目的地在哪  -现在知道了
I thought we didn't know where we're going, dude. we do now.
我也常常做梦
I used to have dreams.
miller医生  miller医生
Dr. miller, dr. miller,
请接总机
Please call the switchboard.
嗨  emily
Hi, emily.
locke夫人  很高兴见到你
Mrs. locke, it's good to see you.
-他怎么样?  -太令人吃惊了  他是我们医院能存活下来的
How is he? he's amazing. he's the youngest preemie
最小的早产儿
To ever survive in this hospital.
他有过感染  患过肺炎  还有其他一些病
He's had infections, pneumonia, you name it.
但是他每次都能挺过去
And every time, he knocked them out.
你们的john是个小战士
He is a fighter, your little john.
太棒了
That's wonderful.
其他护士们都说他是个奇迹宝宝
The other girls say he's a miracle baby.
今天  我们要把他移出保育器了
And today, we're gonna take him out of the incubator
你们终于可以亲手抱一次他了
So you can hold him for the very first time.
我...
I...
我做不到
I can't do this.
我...
I...
对不起  我做不到
I'm sorry. I can't!
我该和谁商量领养的事情
So who do I talk to about adoption?
这儿禁止吸烟  Locke太太
You can't smoke in here, mrs. locke.
当然
Oh. of course.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
他是孩子的父亲吗
Is that the father?
我...
I, uh...
我不认识他
I don't know who that is.
我能问些问题吗
Can I ask you somethin'?
问吧
Sure.
伙计  我为什么跟你们来?
Why am I here, man?
你来  是因为你能看见那个小屋
You're here because you can see the cabin,
正是这样证明了你也很独特
And that makes you special.
我有个理论
Well, I have a theory
关于为什么只有我们才能看见它  我洗耳恭听
As to why we're the only ones who can see it. I'd love to hear it.
我想我们能看到它是因为我们都是疯子
I think we can see it cause we're the craziest.
你怎么知道它现在具体在哪了  伙计
So how'd you figure out where it was, dude?
我还不知道  我们不去小木屋
I didn't. we're not going to the cabin.
我们先去土坑那里
We're gonna make a pit stop first.
土坑?  在哪儿?
Pit stop? where?
Hugo  你就不奇怪达摩组织的那些人怎么了吗
You ever wonder what happened to the dharma initiative, hugo?
这儿起码应该有上百号人
There must have been at least a hundred of 'em
生活在这岛上
Living on this island--
操控站台  修建房屋
Manning the stations, building those homes,
做那些你喜欢的农场服装
Making all that ranch dressing that you like.
但是有一天  他们突然都消失了
And then one day, they're all gone.
就从此消声匿迹了
They just disappeared.
你想知道我们要去哪?
You want to know where we're going?
我们来这他们
We're going to see them.
这里发生了什么
What happened to 'em?
他的杰作
He did.
-你好  -无聊的游戏
Hello! that game's stupid.
他在这  进来吧
He's right in here. come on in.
Melissa  住手!  过来
Melissa, stop that! come on now.
带你弟弟到厨房去
Take your brother in the kitchen.
有人想见见John
There's someone here who wants to see john.
雨下得可真大啊  简直就是瓢泼大雨
It is coming down like cats and dogs out there.
这位好心人想和你谈谈  John
This nice gentleman wants to talk to you, john.
你得好好表现  知道了吗
So I want you on your best behavior. understand?
你请吧
He's all yours.
你喜欢下西洋双陆棋?
You like backgammon?
是吗
Yeah?
看来你对棋的品位还不错
You seem to have a pretty good sense of the game.
john  我叫Richard
I'm richard, john.
我开了一个学校...
I run a school for kids who are...
专为特别儿童建立的
Extremely special,
我有理由相信你也是一个比较特别的孩子
And I have reason to believe that you might be one of them.
介意我给你看一些小东西吗
Mind if I show you a couple of really neat things?
是你画的吗  john
Did you draw that, john?
我想你看一下这些东西
I want you to look at these things...
然后想一想
And think about 'em.
好了  john  现在告诉我
Okay, now tell me, john,
哪样物品是属于你的?
Which of these things belong to you?
给我的吗
T-to keep?
不  不是  John
No, no, john.
哪样物品是已经属于你的了?
Which of these things belong to you already?
John  你确定是刀子吗
Are you sure the knife belongs to you, john?
确定吗
You sure about that?
事实是  他不属于你
Well, it doesn't.
他表现怎样
How did he do?
恐怕John不适合我的学校
I'm afraid john isn't quite ready for our school.
抱歉打扰了
I'm sorry I've wasted your time.
你到底做了些什么
What did you do?
他在下面干什么呢
What's he doing down there?
那...
So...
你就是在这朝Locke开枪  让他自生自灭的地方?
This is where you shot locke and left him for dead, huh?
是的  Hugo  我扣扳机时
Yes, hugo, I was standing right where you are now
正好站在你现在的位置上
When I pulled the trigger.
当时应该发觉到这些都是没有意义的
Should have realized at the time that it was pointless,
但是...  我当时确实头脑不清醒
But... I really wasn't thinking clearly.
也是因为这个原因你杀死了这些人的吗
Is that why you killed all these people, too?
不是我杀的
I didn't kill them.
如果不是"其他人"铲除达摩组织的
Well, if the others didn't wipe out the dharma initiative--
是"其他人"把他们给铲除的  Hugo
They did wipe them out, hugo,
但是这不是我的决定
But it wasn't my decision.
那又会是谁的呢
Then whose was it?
他们首领的
Their leader's.
但是我以为你就是他们的首领
But I thought you were their leader.
不常是
Not always.
小木屋
The cabin?
他当时在建这个小木屋
He was building it.
你找到想要的了吗
Did you find what you were looking for?
是的  Hugo  我想我找到了
Yes, hugo. I believe I did.
钥匙给我
I need your key.
什么?
What?
船长
Captain.
Mayhew刚才死了  医生也无能为力
Mayhew just died. doc couldn't do anything for him.
船员们都在猜想
The crew's asking a lot of questions
你们在岛上发生了什么事
About what happened to you guys over there.
你告诉船员们我自会处理
You tell the crew that I'm dealing with it.
Frank  你可以走了  去给直升机加满燃料
Then you can go gas up the chopper, frank.
-我们要回岛上去  -回去?  为什么?
We're going back. going back? what the hell for?
只管去加燃料  Frank
Gas up the chopper, frank.
那好吧
Okay.
听着  Martin
Listen, martin.
你走后  这又出现了病例
While you were gone, there was some sort of a sickness. mm-hmm.
船员们
The crew--
他们的行为举止都很奇怪
They've been exhibiting some very strange behavior.
Regina自己无故跳到大海里去了
Regina threw herself overboard, for god sake.
如果我不说出来
Now I would be derelict in my duty
因为或许你也染上了这种病
That this might be exactly what's happening to you.
感谢你的关心
I appreciate your concern.
钥匙给我
Give me your key.
协议不允许我...
That's not the protocol--
谢谢
Thank you.
这有两把钥匙的原因
The reason there are two keys
是要我们一起打开保险箱的
Is we're only supposed to open the safe together.
你是在这  不是吗
You're here, aren't you?
那是什么
What is that?
是中级协议
It's the secondary protocol.
上面有什么?
What does it say?
告诉我们Linus的去向
It says where linus is going.
Widmore怎么知道的
How would mr. widmore know that?
因为他是个聪明人
Cause he's a very smart man,
Linus知道我们要把这岛给烧了
And if linus knows that we're gonna torch the island,
他只有一个地方可以去
There's only one place that he can go.
你什么意思  烧毁这岛?
What do you mean, "torch the island"?
这不在协议上
That was not the agreement.
我是答应载你去执行撤退任务
I agreed to ferry you here for an extraction mission.
把我的枪修好
Fix my gun.
这个人
The injured man...
根本不是枪伤
There was no gunshot.
你认为发生了什么
What do you think happened to him?
我不知道  但是当他们再去的时候
I don't know. but when they go back,
-他们会确保不会再发生此事  -Omar
They'll be certain it doesn't happen again. omar!
Keamy要你去武器库
Keamy wants you in the armory.
他叫我死盯这两个人
He said I wasn't supposed to let those two out of my sight.
我来守  去吧
I'll watch them. go.
厨房下面有个储藏室
There's a pantry below our galley
足够容下你们两位
With enough room for two men.
我给你们留下了食物和水  你们得去那
I've left you a supply of food and water. you need to go there.
Michael  死了吗
Michael--is he dead?
没有  不过也差不多了  正因为如此
No, but not for lack of bloody trying, which is precisely why
你们得赶在Keamy回来前藏起来
You two need to be hiding before keamy comes back on this deck.
藏起来是没用的  把救生船给我们
Hiding is pointless. give us your zodiac raft
这样我们就能把岛上的人载回来
So we can start ferrying people back here from the beach.
救我们的唯一办法
The only way to save our lives
是要把我们的人带离那座岛
Is to get our people off that island.
十分钟在货柜后面来见我
Meet me behind the container in ten minutes.
船会给你们送上
The boat will be in the water.
小木屋在这
Cabin's here.
我从这里来  海滩这里
I came from over there. up the coast.
给
Here you go.
喝点水吧  伙计
Drink up, dude.
在一堆乱尸翻了半天  渴死了吧
Digging through dead bodies takes it out of you.
天一会就黑了  Hugo
It's gonna be dark soon, hugo.
如果你朝那个方向走
If you head that way,
你就会到达海滩  你要做的就是
You'll hit the coast, and all you have to do
-一路向北  -你说什么
Is take it north until you reach our beach. uh, what?
我用枪逼你和我们一起  是我不对  Hugo
I forced you to come with us at gunpoint, and I'm sorry, hugo,
但是我相信  你能帮我们找到这
But I was led to believe that we needed you to find this place.
我明白了  现在你有地图了
Oh, I get it. now you got your magic map,
-你  你用不到我了  -我这是给你个机会脱身
You don't-- you don't need me anymore. I'm offering you a chance to leave.
我不想逼你做不情愿的而且相当危险的事
I don't want to put you in harm's way against your will.
那么你觉得我孤身一人
And you think walking through the jungle
-在晚上穿越丛林更加安全?  -我看未必
At night by myself is gonna be any safer? I'm not sure it is.
我想我会和你们一起
I think I'll stick with you guys.
这边吗?
This way?
怎么了?
What?
他现在心甘情愿留下了
He actually thinks staying was his idea.
真行啊  John  你真行啊
Not bad, john. not bad at all.
我和你不一样
I'm not you.
当然不一样
You're certainly not.
放我出去  请放我出去
Somebody, let me out! please let me out.
求求你们  放我...
Please, somebody, let me--
John  你没事吧
John, you okay?
我很好  我很好
I'm fine. I'm fine.
去上课吧  女孩们  上课铃响了
Get to class, ladies. tardy bell just rang.
john你在流血  跟我来
John, you're bleeding. come on.
我们去医务室
Let's go to the nurse's office.
你想说说怎么回事吗?
You wanna talk about it?
不
No.
我知道你很不爽
I know you're probably upset right now,
但是我这确实有些好消息
But I do have some exciting news for you.
最近我接到从波特兰打来的电话
I got a call from portland recently.
那里有家公司
There's a company up there
研究化学和新科技方面
Doing some very exciting things
最前沿的东西
In chemistry and new technologies.
公司叫mittelos研究室
They're called mittelos laboratories.
我和alpert博士谈过了
I spoke with a dr. alpert.
他很有兴趣吸纳
He's very interested in finding young, bright minds
新科技领域的青年俊才
To enter in these new fields of science.
他们想要你参加今年的夏令营
They want you to go to their camp this summer.
科学夏令营?
Science camp?
是的
Yes.
你不知道像科学夏令营这样的东西
Don't you understand that things like science camp
是让我被锁起来的原因
Are the reason why I get stuffed into lockers?
-john 这是千载难逢的机会  -他们怎么知道我的?
John, this is a great opportunity. how do they even know about me?
他们派了代表参加科学博览会
Well, they must have sent a rep to the science fair--
你在costa mesa上进行了展示
Your display at costa mesa.
我不是科学家
I'm not a scientist!
我喜欢拳击  钓鱼和汽车
I like boxing and fishing and cars.
我喜欢运动
I like sports!
我来告诉你一些事情
I'm gonna tell you something--
像你这么大时  我多想有人能告诉我
Something I wish someone had told me at your age.
你可能不想在实验室过一辈子
You might not want to be that guy in the labs
整天和试管  烧杯打交道
Surrounded by test tubes and beakers,
但是那就是你的宿命  John
But that's who you are, john.
你当不了舞会王子
You can't be the prom king.
你不能成为四分卫
You can't be the quarterback.
你成不了超级英雄
You can't be a superhero.
别对我说  我不能做什么
Don't tell me what I can't do.
为什么你不告诉我?
Why didn't you tell me?
告诉你什么?
Tell you what?
你是815航班的幸存者
That you're a survivor of 815.
因为你不会相信我
Aah! 'cause you wouldn't have believed me.
你认为我不会相信你?
You didn't think I'd believe you?
我告诉你  我是这个世界上唯一
I tell you that I'm one of the only people in the world
认为那架在海底的飞机残骸
That think that that plane
是一个骗局
On the bottom of the ocean is a hoax,
-你还认为我不会相信你?  -我不知道我能否信任你
And you didn't think I'd believe you? I didn't know if I could trust you.
是你老板把那假的飞机弄到海底的
Your boss put that plane there.
伙计  我也以为我是他们的同伙
Man, I thought I was mr. conspiracy,
不过明白我的意思了吧
But you got me beat there.
听我说  听我说
Listen to me. listen to me.
你不能把那些人送回去  keamy
You can't fly that guy back--keamy.
-让我来应付keamy吧  好吗?  -你不能把他带回去
You let me worry about keamy, all right? you can't fly him back!
他会杀掉岛上的所有人
He is gonna kill everyone on that island.
所有人
Everyone.
你的良心不会让它发生  伙计
And you don't want that on your conscience, man.
相信我
Trust me.
我刚好要把他带到驾驶仓
Just getting him down to the engine room.
朝305方位前进
Stay on a heading of exactly 3-0-5.
Faraday说  只有这条路是安全的
Faraday says that's the only safe way to and from the boat.
如果Keamy发现这个东西不见了  你要怎么解释
What will you tell keamy if he notices the zodiac is missing?
我会告诉他  是你偷了  走吧
I'll tell him you stole it. now go.
Desmond
Desmond.
-我不能和你一起走  -为什么不?
I can't go with you. why not?
我在那个岛上三年了
I've been on that island for three years.
我再也不要踏上那个小岛了
I'm never setting foot on it again...
penny正在找我  我更不能回去
Not when penny's coming for me.
我会随第一组尽早回来
I'll be back with the first group as soon as I can.
径直往那个方向去  知道了吗?
Stay on that bearing, yeah?
我会的
I will.
你得走了
You need to go now.
从这走约200码
It should be about 200 yards this way.
你确定在那边吗  John?
You sure it's gonna be there, john?
什么?
I'm sorry?
那个木屋  如果搬走了  怎么办?
The cabin-- what if it's moved again?
不会的
It hasn't moved
因为我所知道的  就是在那
Because I was told that this is where it would be.
我也被告知很多事情
I was told a lot of things, too--
我是被选中的  我和你们不一样
That I was chosen, that I was special.
结果我的脊骨上却长了个瘤
I end up with a tumor on my spine
我的双手沾满了我女儿的血
And my daughter's blood all over my hands.
Ben  我对发生的一切感到抱歉
I'm sorry those things happened to you, ben.
那些事情注定要发生的
Those things had to happen to me.
那是我的宿命
That was my destiny.
你很快就会明白了
But you'll understand soon enough
被选中是需要付出代价的...
That there are consequences to being chosen...
John  因为  命运
Because, destiny, john,
是个薄情的婊子
Is a fickle bitch.
伙计们
Guys?
木屋
Cabin.
好的  好的  好的  干得好  伙计
Okay, okay, okay. good job, man.
干得好  John  好了  我们明天继续
Good job, john. okay, we'll try it some more tomorrow.
他是你的了  起来吧
He's all yours. come on up.
好了  来吧
It's all right. come on.
别放弃  Locke先生
Don't give up, mr. locke.
你说什么?
Excuse me?
我说  别放弃
I'm just saying, don't give up.
凡事皆有可能
Anything's possible.
你应该去看看我的档案
You should read my file.
我的脊柱粉碎了
My spine was crushed.
双脚不能恢复知觉的可能性高达98%
There's a 98% chance I'll never get any feeling back in my legs.
所以我想不通  为什么我还在尝试
So I don't know why I'm even trying to--
实际上  我已经读过你的档案
As a matter of fact, I did read your file.
你从八层楼摔下  却得以幸存
You survived falling eight stories out of a building.
这已经是个奇迹  Locke先生
That's a miracle, mr. locke.
让我来问你
Let me ask you something.
你相信奇迹吗?
Do you believe in miracles?
不  我不相信
No. I don't believe in miracles.
你应该相信
You should.
我身上就发生过一个
I had one happen to me.
听着  我只想回我的房间
Hey, look. I just want to go back to my room.
你知道你需要什么吗 locke先生?
You know what you need, mr. locke?
你需要来次徒步旅行
You need to go on a walkabout.
什么是徒步旅行
Wha-what's a walkabout?
那是个自我发现的旅程
It's a journey of self-discovery.
你要深入澳大利亚的腹地
You go out into the australian outback
除了刀子和你的智慧  什么也不要带
With nothing more than a knife and your wits.
徒步旅行什么的  我做不到
I can't "walkabout" anything.
我是个瘸子  要是你还没看出来的话
In case you haven't noticed, I'm a cripple.
你真的是这样而已吗  locke先生？
Is that what you are, mr. locke?
徒步旅行前我是一个普通的人
I went on my walkabout convinced I was one thing,
回来的时候成了另外一个人
But I came back another.
我发现了我的本质  发现我是谁
I found out what I was made of, who I was.
看看你现在
And here you are,
一个勤务员
An orderly.
John  我不只是个勤务员
Oh, I'm a lot more than just an orderly, john.
当你准备好了  locke先生
When you're ready, mr. locke...
你就会相信我所说的
You'll listen to what I'm saying.
要是碰巧再次见面...
And then when you and me run into each other again...
你就欠我一个人情
You'll owe me one.
医生
Hey, doc.
有些不可思议的事  有没兴趣听听?
Wanna hear something weird?
当然
Yeah, sure.
你知道我从海滩上获得的摩尔斯密码吗
You know that morse code message that I got from the beach?
密码说医生死了  被冲上了岸边
It said that the doctor washed up on the shore
喉咙被切开了
With his throat slit.
可我不是还好好的吗
But I'm the doctor.
很荒唐  对吧?
Crazy, right?
所有的都在这了吗?
Everything here?
是的  先生
Yes, sir.
好  把它装好
Good. get it packed up.
把这些都搬出来  准备干嘛呢
What are you gonna do with all that?
发动直升机  Frank
Fire her up, frank.
Mr. Keamy  我是受雇来运送科学家的
Mr. keamy, I was hired to fly scientists.
滚到机舱去把直升机发动起来  Frank
Get your ass in the cockpit and fire up the chopper, frank.
我不会载你去的
I'm not taking you.
-我会杀了你的  Frank  -是吗  那就杀吧
I'll kill you, frank. yeah, well, you do that,
但你永远都不可能再回到岛上了
You'll never get back to the island
因为这里只有我一个飞行员
Cause I'm the only pilot you got.
抱歉  医生
Sorry, doc.
改变主意了吗  Frank?
That change anything, frank? huh?
再过三十秒  就轮到下个倒霉鬼了
Another 30 seconds goes by and someone else's turn--
你的枪我修好了
I fixed your gun.
往后站  martin  不然我就开枪了
Now stand down, martin, or I will fire.
你不会这么做的  船长
I don't think you want to do that, captain.
他手臂上绑着什么
What's that on his arm?
决定的怎么样了?  Frank?
What'll it be, frank?
我们去
We're flying.
快点  出发了  小伙子们  快
Come on. let's go, boys. come on!
把剩下的武器都搬上去  出发  出发
Get the rest of the weapons onboard, and let's go. let's go!
我们走吧
Let's get out of here.
出发
Let's move out.
谢谢  船长
Thanks, captain.
快  快  快  出发
Come on! come on! come on! come on! let's go!
我跟你怎么说来着
What did I say to you?
你叫我别离开帐篷
You told me not to leave my tent.
我饿了
I was hungry.
Jack  你得好好休息  你不能再到处乱跑了
Jack, you have to rest. you can't run around.
我知道你不好意思开口
I know that it is hard for you to ask for help,
但要是你把缝线拆了
But if you tear your stitches...
行了  行了  我知道了
Okay. okay. I got it.
医生是最难对付的病人
Doctors make the worst patients.
Jack!
我想他们是叫我们跟过去
I think they want us to follow 'em.
好了  我们进去吧
All right. let's do this.
那里面  我就不去了
I'm not going in there with you.
什么
What?
这个小岛要我病倒
The island wanted me to get sick,
它要你恢复健康
And it wanted you to get well.
我的时代结束了  John
My time is over, john.
你的时代到来了
It's yours now.
你要是一个人进去  我也没有意见
Yeah, I'm cool with you going in alone, too.
祝你好运  John
Good luck, john.
你是Jacob?
Are you jacob?
但我可以代表他说话
But I can speak on his behalf.
那  你是谁
Well, who are you?
我叫Christian
I'm christian.
你知道我为什么来这吗
You know why I'm here?
当然
Yeah, sure.
你自己知道吗
Do you?
我来这...
I'm here...
是因为我是被选中的
Because I was chosen to be.
确实如此
That's absolutely right.
Claire?
嗨  John
Hi, john.
你怎么在这里
What are you doing here?
别担心  我跟着他  好着呢
Don't worry. I'm fine. I'm with him.
孩子呢
Where's the baby?
孩子待在他该待的地方
The baby's where he's supposed to be,
不过不在这
And that's not here.
你最好
It's probably best
不要跟别人说  她在这
That you don't tell anyone that you saw her.
-为什么  为什么她  -我们没时间聊这些了
Why? why is she-- we don't have time for this.
船上的人已经在回来的路上了
The people from the boat are already on their way back,
一旦他们抵达这
And once they get here,
所有的问题都会变得毫无意义
All of these questions won't matter one bit.
那你怎么不问个有意义的问题
So why don't you ask the one question that does matter?
我该怎么拯救岛上的人
How do I save the island?
他告诉你   我们该怎么做了吗
Did he tell you what we're supposed to do?
他要我们离开这里
He wants us to move the island.
==============| YYeTs字幕组招募启示 |==============
英文字幕录制(居住在加拿大和美国) 双语字幕校正 时间轴调整
英语翻译 欧美影视新闻翻译 影视评论 论坛版主 美工人员
服务器提供者 发布宣传 联系地址：www.YYeTs.net
==== YYeTs属于网络爱好者组织 加入者仅凭个人兴趣爱好 无报酬 ====